Guide to the Peter McCandless papers, 1978-1992
George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
Peter McCandless papers
1978-1992
George Mason University. Special Collections and Archives.
Peter McCandless
C0163
16.75 linear feet (34 boxes)
The Peter McCandless papers contain material relating to Reston, Virginia. The majority of the documents are from the Reston Land Corporation and include correspondence, awards and gifts given to Reston, project reports, newsclippings, press releases, marketing and promotional material.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Donated by Peter McCandless in 1992.
Biographical Information
Reston is a planned community in Northern Virginia. Robert E. Simon, Jr. was the founder of Reston, and he purchased the land with the proceeds from the sale of Carnegie Hall in New York City in 1961. Construction began in 1963 with the building of Lake Anne. Then Gulf Oil Corporation formed a subsidiary, Reston Gulf, Inc., in 1967 and took complete financial and operational control. When the Mobil Corporation bought the remaining undeveloped land from Gulf Reston in 1978, Reston Land Corporation was formed as a subsidiary. Peter McCandless served as a publicist who worked with developers to market Reston and also co-wrote with Thomas Grubisich, "Reston: The First Twenty Years" (1985).
Scope and Content
The Peter McCandless papers contains material relating to Reston, Virginia. The majority of the documents are from the Reston Land Corporation and include correspondence, awards and gifts given to Reston, project reports, newsclippings, press releases, marketing and promotional material.
Series one is titled Correspondence. Included in this series are memoranda and other correspondence relating to Reston, particularly Reston Land Corporation. Some of the subjects of the correspondence includes action reports and the Planned Community Archives. The series is dated from 1983 to 1990 and is contained within boxes 1 through 4.
Series two has information relating to awards that were given to Reston. Among the awards were National Sales and Marketing Council Awards, Finest for Family Living Awards, Three Blue Ribbons to Reston Offices and others. The series is dated from 1983 to 1990 and is contained in box 4.
Series three documents the gifts that were given to Reston, many from the Mobil Foundation. Included among the gifts are Mobil Foundation gift to the Reston Players, Reston Land Corporation Gift of $1000 to Fairfax County Vocational Education Foundation and others. The series is dated from 1984 to 1989 and is contained in box 5.
Series four consists of reports on different projects in Reston. Included in the series are Reston Town Center Phase One Partnership, McCandless Company Public Relations Plan For Reston Land and other projects. The series is dated from 1978 to 1990 and is contained within boxes 6 and 7.
The information in series five relates to marketing plans for Reston and Reston Land Corporation. Included in the series are Public Relations Programs Marketing Part I and II, North Hills Marketing and other plans. The series is dated from 1984 to 1990 and is contained within boxes 7 through 11.
Series six is titled News Releases. The documents in this series are news releases on different events or proceedings in Reston. Among the documents there is information on Northern Virginia Builders Association, promotions, Reston Roadways Beautification and others. The series is dated from 1980 to 1990 and is contained in boxes 11 through 14.
Series seven is titled Reston Land Corporation Newsclippings. This is the largest series in the collection. Included in the collection are newsclippings to the Reston Land Corporation over the years 1986 to 1992 from different newspapers. The series is contained in boxes 14 through 29.
Series eight is titled General Information and is the last series in this collection. The series contains a variety of topics including current media lists, House Beautiful Reston Land Corporation 20th Anniversary, NASA in Reston and others. The series is dated from 1979 to 1990 and is contained in boxes 29 through 34.
Arrangement
Organized into eight series.
Series 1: Correspondence, 1983-1990 (Boxes 1-4)
Series 2: Awards, 1983-1990 (Boxes 4)
Series 3: Gifts, 1984-1989 (Boxes 5)
Series 4: Reports, 1978-1990 (Boxes 6-7)
Series 5: Marketing, 1984-1990 (Boxes 7-11)
Series 6: News Releases, 1980-1990 (Boxes 11-14)
Series 7: Reston Land Corporation Newsclippings, 1986-1992 (Boxes 14-29)
Series 8: General Information, 1979-1990 (Boxes 29-34)
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
The Special Collections and Archives also holds the Planned Community Archives and other personal papers and organizational records that document Reston, Virginia, and other planned communities.
Index Terms
Persons:
McCandless, Peter.
Corporate Names:
Reston Land Corporation.
Geographical Names:
Reston (Va.)
Subjects:
Housing--Virginia--Reston.; Planned communities--Virginia--Reston.
Contents List
- Series 1: Correspondence, 1983-1990; (3.5 boxes)
  Included in this series are memoranda and other correspondence relating to Reston, particularly Reston Land Corporation.
  - Reston Land Corporation Memorandums, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    279.5
  - Reston Land Corporation Correspondence, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    279.6
  - Reston Land Corporation Industrial Economic Boom, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    286.3
  - Reston Land Corporation Correspondence, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    282.8
  - House Beautiful-Media Advisory, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    278.2
    - Shooting A One-of-a-Kind Shot: the best 1,500 square feet in America, June 8, 1984; 1.
  - Miscellaneous, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    278.1
    - Reston Profile Series: Fairfax County/ Reston Schools, December 28, 1983; 1.
  - Northern Virginia Builders Association Action magazine Premier Issue Cover Story, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    278.5
  - Hazel/Peterson Companies, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    277.10
  - Correspondence, 19843 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    277.12
  - Miscellaneous, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    277.13
  - Chrono Reading File, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    285.3
  - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    2803
  - Action Reports, Memorandums, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    283.1
  - Planned Community Archives, Incorporated, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    289.7
  - Regardie's, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    287.1a
  - Regardie's, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    287.1b
  - The Greater Reston-Media Support, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    287.2
  - Harley-Wood, Incorporated/Builder Magazine, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    287.4
  - Reston Land Corporation, Newsletter File, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Reston Land Corporation Correspondence, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    286.1
  - Reston Tour, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    286.7
  - Realtor Month Attracts 430 Area Developers, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    285.1
  - Dedication: Vernon J. Walker Nature Center, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    291.11
  - Planned Community Archives-Anniversary Parties, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    290.7
  - Miscellaneous, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    289.5
  - Reston Land Corporation Newsletter (With Biddison and Company), 1987 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    285.5
  - Planned Community Archives, Incorporated, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    289.6
    - Letter Referencing PCA-GMU Partnership, September 1986; 1.
    - PLANNED COMMUNITY ARCHIVES, INC.: Minutes of the Meeting of the Board of Directors, 22 September 1986; 35.
    - PLANNED COMMUNITY ARCHIVES, INC.: SUMMARY OF OBJECTIVES AND ACTIVITIES, ca. 1986; 50.
  - Letters, Memorandums and Action Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    295.1
  - Reston Land Corporation Memorandums, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    299.1
  - Reston Town Center Association, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    298.3
- Series 2: Awards, 1983-1990; (0.5 box)
  The series has information relating to awards that were given to Reston. Among the awards were National Sales and Marketing Council Awards, Finest for Family Living Awards and others.
  - Reston Land Corporation Wins Two Mame Marketing Awards for Programs, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    455.2
  - Reston Land Corporation Wins Two Mame Awards, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    277.2
    - Reston Land Wins Two MAME Marketing Awards For 1993 Programs, June 22, 1984; 1.
  - Reston Triathlon Winners Awarded, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    282.4
  - National Association of Home Builders; and National Sales and Marketing Council Awards, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    281.1
  - Reston Recognized by American Institute of Architects, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    281.6
  - Awards Release Reston Land Corporation, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    291.6
  - Northern Virginia/National Association of Industrial and Office Parks Awards Three Blue Ribbons to Reston Offices, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    294.2
  - Reston Land Corporation Wins Gold at International Advertisement Festival, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    294.3
  - Finest For Family Living Awards, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    293.10
  - Reston Land Corporation Honored at Annual Inby Awards Luncheon, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    297.5
  - Exceptional Design Awards, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    297.10
    - Tetra's Pond Office Building Wins Highest Award in Exceptional Design Awards Program, 25 July 1989; 1.
    - Tetra's Award Winning Pond Office Building, 1989; 6.
  - Westfield International Conference Center Honored with Northern Virginia/National Association Industrial and Office Parks Award of Excellence, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    297.18
  - Cardillo Wins "Treasure Homes", 1989 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    297.19
  - Reston Board of Commerce Launches Business Service Awards Program, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    298.9
  - Mame Awards Ceremony, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    299.11
- Series 3: Gifts, 1984-1989; (1 box)
  This series documents the gifts that were given to Reston, many from the Mobil Foundation. Included among the gifts are Mobil Foundation gift to the Reston Players and others.
  - Mobil Gifts to Salvation Army and Reston Chorale, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    277.6
  - Mobil Foundation Gift to the Reston Players, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    277.5
  - Mobil Foundation Gift to Junior Achievement, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    277.4
  - Mobil Foundation Presents Holiday Gifts to the Reston Chorale, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    455.12
  - Mobil Foundation Says Merry Christmas to the Salvation Army, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    455.11
  - Mobil Foundation Presents Gifts to Junior Achievement, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    455.10
  - Reston Land Corporation Gives $500 to Junior Achievement, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    281.8
  - Reston Land Corporation Gift of $2500 to Grace Art Gallery, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    281.7
  - Mobil Foundation Gives $5000 to Very Special Arts Festival, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    281.5
  - Reston Land Corporation Gives $1000 to Fairfax County Vocational Education Foundation, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    281.4
  - Mobil Foundation $3000 to Reston Institute for the Arts, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    281.3
  - Mobil Gifts to Reston Players, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    282.5
  - Mobil Gifts to Reston Interfaith, Incorporated, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    282.3
  - Mobil Gift to YMCA, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    282.2
  - Mobil Grant to Reston Players, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    284.12
  - Mobil Land Development Gives $1500 to Reston Interfaith, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    284.11
  - Mobil Foundation Gift to YMCA, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    284.10
  - Mobil Foundation Gives $500 to Junior Achievement, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    284.7
  - Mobil Foundation Gives $500 to Fairfax County Vocation Education, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    284.6
  - Grace Art Gallery Receives Mobil Foundation Gift of $2500, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    284.4
  - Mobil Foundation Gift to Reston Interfaith, 19847 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    291.4
  - Mobil Gifts to Fairfax County Vocation Education, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    294.8
  - Mobil Foundation Gift to YMCA, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    296.11
  - Northern Virginia/National Association of Industrial and Office Parks Gives 2nd $10000 to George Mason University/Chair in Local Government, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    296.10
  - Mobil Gift to Fellowship Square, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    297.20
  - Mobil's 20th Birthday Gift/Interfaith, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    297.13
    - Mobil's Twentieth Birthday Gift to Reston Interfaith (News Release), September 8, 1989; 1.
  - Grace Art Gallery Receives $2500 from Mobil, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    297.9
  - Mobil Contribution to Reston Community Players, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    297.8
- Series 4: Reports, 1978-1990; (1.5 boxes)
  The reports are information from different projects in Reston. Included in the series are Reston Town Center Phase One Partnership and other projects.
  - The Case for Relocating the Fairfax County Government Headquarters to Reston, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    456.5
    - Paper: Gulf Reston, Inc./Gladstone Associates, "The Case for Relocating the Fairfax County Government Headquarters to Reston", January 1978; 1.
  - Reston Land Corporation Reports, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    279.7
  - Dulles Parallel Lanes (Planning and Strategy), 1984 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    288.4
  - Reston Board of Commerce Program Committee, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    288.6
  - Reston Land Corporation Public Relations Planning, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    288.5
  - Development Produces New Records, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    284.3
  - Reston Designers' Showcase, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    286.4
  - Planned Community Archives, Incorporated, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    290.1
  - Year of Living Splendidly, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    289.4
  - Reston Business Center Absorption Breaks All REcords, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    286.6
  - Residential Sales Post Best First Half Year Record, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    284.9
  - Reston Town Center Phase One Partnership, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    292.6
  - Reston Forum, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    290.3
  - McCandless Company Public Relations Plan For Reston Land, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    296.5
  - Reston Board of Commerce-Research Final Quarter, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    295.5a
    - RBC Membership Development Committee Proposed Implementation Plan, October 12, 1988; 50.
  - Reston Board of Commerce-Research Final Quarter, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    295.5b
  - Reston Land Corporation-Action Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    295.2
  - 2nd Record Breaking Year, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    299.20
- Series 5: Marketing, 1969-1990; (4.5 boxes)
  The information in this series relates to marketing plans for Reston and Reston Land Corporation. Included in the series are North Hills Marketing and other plans.
  - Here's What's Happening At Houston Park on Gulf Reston's Behalf, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    457.2
  - Gulf Oil Real Estate Development Company, 1980s (Box 7, Folder 12)
    457.9
    - Brochure: "A Straightforward Message from: Gulf Oil Real Estate Development Company", no date; 1.
  - North Point Village, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    457.7
    - Magazine: House Beautiful Magazine, Best Small House 1984 Issue, October 1984; 1.
  - National Publications, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    457.1
    - Article: Charles McDowell, The Star-Ledger, "From Little Seed Grows a Big City", August 11, 1965; 1.
    - Article: Wolf Von Eckardt, "The Row House is Going to Town-Not to Mention Country," Washington Post, July 24, 1966; 2.
    - Booklet: Gulf Reston, Inc., A Brief History of Reston, Virginia, January 1970; 3.
    - Booklet: Gulf Reston, Inc., A Brief History of Reston, Virginia, July 1973; 4.
    - Magazine: The Reston Letter, Season of Success Issue, January 1967; 5.
    - Newsletter: Columbia Real Estate, Title and Insurance Company, June 1967; 6.
  - House Beautiful, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    457.10
    - Information Sheet: House Beautiful Magazine, "House Beautiful's "Best Small House '84", 1984; 1.
    - Photograph: Feliciano, "Bedroom Number Two," House Beautiful Magazine, 1984; 2.
    - Photograph: Feliciano, "Compact Kitchen," House Beautiful Magazine, 1984; 3.
    - Photograph: Feliciano, "Living Room," House Beautiful Magazine, 1984; 4.
    - Photograph: Feliciano, "Upstairs Bonus Room," House Beautiful Magazine, 1984; 5.
    - Press Release: Reston Land Corporation, "Fact Sheet", 1984; 6.
    - Press Release: Reston Land Corporation, "Felix Construction Corporation, Warren Katz", 1984; 7.
    - Press Release: Reston Land Corporation, "One-Of-A-Kind House in America Opens in Reston", June 28, 1984; 8.
  - Wolf Von Eckardt/Time Magazine Reston Revisited, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    288.2
  - Reston/Burke Connection Marketing, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    288.1
  - Reston Home Owner Association/Public Relations Marketing Communication, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    288.3
  - Reston At Twenty: Marketing, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    286.5
  - Reston Land Corporation Was Named Marketing Man of Year, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    280.6
  - Richardson Promoted/Development, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    293.7
  - Reston Land Corporation Marketing Planning, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    287.7
  - Reston Land Corporation "Moveable Feast" Promotion, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    286.8a
  - Reston Land Corporation "Moveable Feast" Promotion, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    286.8b
  - Reston Land Corporation-Residential Marketing Newsletter, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    285.4
  - Community Services Profile, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    293.1
  - Reston Land Corporation: Marketing Planning (Public Relations), 1987 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    293.3
  - Reston Land Corporation Newsletter, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    293.2
  - Reston Land Corporation Written Publicity, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    293.6
  - Reston Land Corporation Marketing Profile: Population, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    292.1
  - Reston Land Corporation Marketing Profile: Transportation, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    292.3
  - Reston Land Corporation Marketing Profile: Reston Schools, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    292.5
  - D'Alesandro Promoted, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    291.3
  - Public Relations Programs Marketing Part I, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    290.5
  - Public Relations Programs Marketing Part II, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Reston's Ten Million Square Feet/Commercial, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    296.2
  - Marketing Plan, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    291.1
  - In Progress: Reston Land Corporation, Rotary House/Acorn, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    290.6
  - Reston Spring Fling and Promotional Material, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    457.6
  - Marketing Material (Including Urban Land Institute Award), 1989 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    298.2
  - Urban Land Institute: Marketing and Public Relation, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    296.3
  - Tetra-Jeff Coho Release, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    296.7
  - North Hills Marketing, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    293.4
  - Mobil Gift to Fellowship Square Foundation, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    295.15
  - Reston's New $6 million North Gateway, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    299.10
  - Atkins Appointed Loveless, Vice President, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    299.17
  - Reston Advertisements, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    457.3
    - Brochure: Reston Land Corporation, "Reston: The Best in Northern Virginia", 1990; 1.
  - Westfields-International Conference Center, 1990s (Box 11, Folder 4)
    457.8
  - Reston Land Corporation Promotional Material, 1990s (Box 11, Folder 5)
    456.7
    - 1991 FACTS: POPULATION, ca. 1991; 1.
    - ARTS: Promotional Brochure, February 1991; 2.
    - CHILD CARE: Promotional Brochure, February 1991; 3.
    - COMMUNITY SERVICES: Promotional Brochure, February 1991; 4.
    - Reston Map, 1990; 8.
    - Reston Master Plan (Map), 1988; 9.
    - What is Reston Land Corporation, ca. 1990; 10.
    - TRANSPORTATION (Promotional Brochure, February 1991; 21.
    - Reston Town Center, 1990; 28.
- Series 6: News Releases, 1980-1990; (3 boxes)
  The documents in this series are news releases on different events or proceedings in Reston. Among the news releases there is information on Northern Virginia Builders Association, promotions and others.
  - Hunterlabs II-Groundbreaking, 1980s (Box 11, Folder 6)
    287.3
  - Reston Land Corporation-Press Releases, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    455.4
  - Reston Land Corporation Press Releases, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    455.5
  - Richardson, Carter, Steiner Promoted, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    285.2
  - Reston Job Growth, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    455.3
    - Survey Reveals 35% Reston Job Growth - Highest in Twenty Years, October 29, 1984; 1.
  - First American-Best Year in History, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    281.2
  - William S. Lottier Joins Reston Land Corporation, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    277.1
    - William S. Lottier Joins Reston Land Corporation, June 11, 1984; 1.
  - Survey Reveals 35% Job Growth, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    277.3
  - Stienbauer and Cleveland Promoted, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    277.7
    - Key Corporate Changes Announced, July 9, 1984; 1.
  - Farrar and Elkjer Promotions, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    277.11
  - Northern Virginia Builders Association (NVBA)/Major Achievements in marketing Excellence (MAME) 4x Blue Ribbons, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    282.6
  - Reston Land Corporation Press Releases, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    455.6
  - Key Corporate Changes Announced, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    282.1
  - Mobil Foundation/Reston Choral, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    282.7
  - Builders' House, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    280.1
  - Reston Land Corporation Press Releases, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    455.7
  - Tom D'Alesandro Joins the Reston Land Corporation, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    289.2
  - Reston Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    284.1
  - Mobil Foundation Pays Holiday Tribute to Reston Choral, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    284.13
  - Phil Luna to Manager of Engineering, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    284.8
  - Linda Miller Joins Reston Land Corporation, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Reston Land Corporation Press Releases, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    455.8
  - Seitz Appointed Plan Analyst, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    294.11
  - National Association of Homebuilder's Institute for Residential Marketing (MIRM) Awards Silver, Steiner, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    294.12
  - Hinchee Release, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    291.5
  - Lee Sammis Association Named 68th Largest, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    292.8
  - Fame Is the Name of Major Achievement in Marketing Excellence (MAME), 1987 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    291.10
  - Frutchey Named Reston Land Corporation Manager, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    291.9
  - Chorale Release, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    291.8
  - Buckner Release, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    291.7
  - "Elbow Room" Strikes Silver in Dallas, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    289.1
  - Reston Land Corporation Press Releases, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    455.9
  - Tate Promoted to Accountant Manager, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    294.5
  - Reston Land Corporation Hires Nancy Hughes, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    294.4
  - Grace Art Gallery Release, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    294.10
  - YMCA Release, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    294.9
  - Elkjer and Hagelis Promoted, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    294.7
  - Houser, Hastie Join Mobil Land Development Corporation (MLDC), 1988 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    294.6
  - Mobil Gift to Interfaith, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    293.9
  - Reston Land Corporation Press Releases, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    456.1
    - Press Release: McCandless Company, "Robinson Wins Virginia Lions 41st Bland Music Competition", June 21, 1989; 1.
    - Press Release: Reston Land Corporation, "Cardillo Walks off With Homes of Reston Treasure", November 10, 1989; 2.
    - Press Release: Reston Land Corporation, "CentralPark at Reston Town Center: Brilliant Inauguration of Sophisticated Urban Living in Reston's Town Center", August 17, 1989; 3.